Diego Mitma Ariza

Frontend Developer Jr. | I Industrial Engineer

Contact Information

diego89ma@gmail.com



51 992 998 907



linkedin.com/in/diegomitari/



github.com/DiegoMitari



portfolio-diegomitari.vercel.app/

Education

JavaScript Developer

Coderhouse

Sept 2021 - Nov 2021

Industrial Engineering

National University of San Marcos

2008 - 2015

Developed Projects

Credit Simulator | Fintech Bank

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap y JQuery

FreeCodeCamp Clone

React, Javascript, HTML y CSS

Landing Page 01

HTML, CSS, Flexbox

Job Search - Web

React, Javascript, HTML y CSS

Employment History

Deister Software Perú

Jr. Developer Analyst

Jun 2022 - Current

Ramagro (Grupo Gloria) Warehouse Assistant

May 2019 - Aug 2022

Cencosud Retail Perú

Inventory Analyst

Nov 2016 - Oct 2018

Molitalia Stock Analyst Jun 2015 - Nov 2016

Profile

Frontend Developer Jr. in continuous learning.

After more than 6 years working as an Industrial Engineer I found my true passion in Web

Development.

I consider myself a curious and self-taught person, adaptable to change and focused on building solutions.

Courses

CSS (Flexbox, CSS Grid,

Bootstrap)

Udemy

React JS | Vue JS

Platzi

PostgreSQL

Netzun

Skills

HTML

Figma

CSS

Node JS

JavaScript

React JS

Bootstrap

Vue 3

TailwindCSS

PotsgreSQL

Languages

English B1 Portuguese A1